I carry high my craven flag,
my ally I'm gonna fly and let my
struggles shoot me through the sky!
It'd be a pity if we
lingered here and let our
pretty sparks of life
blend aloud and disappear?
There may be fog that even
you can't navigate If someone
strong like you is lost then
who will set me straight?
Cause when the waves
cast, my heart exists.
It's been your kindness and your strength.
That would free me from the mist.
And just like that.
We move on!
Sail to a new dawn.
Weigh anchor, ride as high as you can.
I assure, I don't need anger.
I go fast as I am, yeah.
I hear you laughing like
you're numb to it all.
Well, we're dashing together.
No, we're never gonna fall, you know.
The whole world may now be my enemy.
Water swirl, but I ain't backing
down so long as I'm free.
Thought I'll give it, come
round the current with me.
All in, wake up bright and
early, making for the peak we go.
Luffy, please wait!
You can do this!
I trust you!
But whatever doesn't work!
I can't do it!
You ready?
Give me your worst Straw Hat!
I've been waiting!
That bird!
You don't need to hold me down.
A dragon doesn't run from a rat.
Let me tell you a story
Straw Hat 20 years ago the
people of guano watched their
hero boil and their country
burn ever since then they
have prayed for a new hero
and now here you are I'm
begging to meet the same end.
Flame, Dragon Torch!
You're not gonna throw that punch.
I'll melt you alive!
Before you even get the chance?
Rattles!
Reef!
Turtle!
The heat you can't melt me.
The old man taught me how to throw
a punch without even touching you.
I believe I know what
you mean by Haki now.
It's called Rio in the land of Wano.
You're over stressing yourself.
Allow the Haki to move to your fist
from the parts that don't use it.
You'll never hurt my friends again!
Turn your hands!
Blazing Dragon!
Come, come!
Come, come, ride!
Play, Back!
Ah!
Wait, that light!
What the hell's going on up there?
What just happened?
You've got this!
Yo!
Give him hell, Straw Hat!
It's time to end this!
And it's him!
Take him down!
For Wano!
We're counting on you!
I'm counting on you.
Let me prove!
Onward!
To Kuri!
Oh, yeah.
My lord!
Hurry!
Don't look back! Run!
Those fools think I don't
know what they're up to.
They're headed to Kuri.
The heir to the Kozuki clan
is waiting at their castle.
Go kill the little brat.
Kill his whole family while you're there.
Wipe them out.
We'll exterminate their clan.
Odin has children.
Better go finish things up then.
You may have killed Lord Odin, but
we won't let you kill his family.
Move.
If anyone is stupid enough to stand
against the Shogun, then shoot them dead!
Do you idiots understand now?
The true death of my grudge!
Now suffer!
Burn in hell!
You'll all die along with
your beloved Kozuki's!
Do you know what happened to Odin's wife?
We confirmed her death in Bekori town.
No one else escaped the castle.
Their accursed clan is gone at last!
Now, time, y 'all!
Time for all of you to make a choice!
Will you stand beside me
in service of this land?
Or will you go to war?
You know damn well what we'll say.
You'll never be shogun!
We are loyal to the Kozuki clan alone!
We will avenge Odin's death
no matter what it takes!
The land of water will not fall today!
Show no fear!
Onward
What is that strange light?
Last breath
Everyone run!
I had no idea you were so weak.
You called yourself Samurai.
Or maybe Samurai weren't
worth a damn to begin with.
To think that you looked down on me.
Who's the fool now?
I'm on the throne and you're burning
to death in a battle you can't win.
Face it!
The weak can't protect a damn thing!
Now, as for the rest of the
country, I have an announcement!
This is a new Wano, painted in
the calendar of the Kurozumi!
You're gonna pay!
All able-bodied men, I've
got a new job for you.
Daddy, no!
Give me back my dad!
Don't take him away from me!
What's that?
No, please don't shoot! Please let him go!
It's going to be all right.
Daddy!
You will all work to produce weapons.
Put your back into it, slackers!
You're gonna work until you're dead!
We're going to storm.
We can't grow crops in this soil.
Some thirst.
I'm sorry.
There's nothing to eat.
Nothing to drink.
This land is a living hell.
Someone help us!
I beg of you.
Help us, please!
If you want to live,
you better keep moving!
Those goods are more important
than your worthless lives!
Drop them in your death!
This country is closed off from the world.
Scream as loud as you want!
No one will come to help you.
I can't take it anymore.
I'd rather die than do this another day.
We need you.
We must survive the coming winter.
A long cold night.
Do not lose faith in Lady Toki's words.
Now
that's funny. Look.
I know those filthy
swine will eat anything.
Even and I'll reject smile fruits.
Go on, eat up.
Then laugh till you die.
You'll be just like Ebisu Town.
Even when you're starving
and mourning your loved ones,
you'll keep laughing like fools.
You're nothing but maggots, so I'm sure
you'll keep eating the trash I dump on you.
Aren't you glad I gave you
all the gift of laughter?
Now no one has to listen to you cry.
Starts the banquet!
Eat your film!
Every pleasure is yours!
I thought I'd be dead or dead!
I thought I'd be all alone!
You know Komurasaki, I had
everything, exactly as I wanted it.
You're telling me you
worked at the pleasure
hall all that time just
to get revenge on me?
You're nothing but a slut.
I'll die, but I'm taking
you with me, Komurasaki!
That's the price of your betrayal.
You can serve me a drink in hell.
Foxfire Kin'emon and the Akazaya Samuil.
If they want to challenge
us, then I welcome it.
I'll send them right back to
their graves with a single stroke.
This is pandemonium.
I can't move Onigashima!
I never could!
What should I do?
I tried my best, but I'm useless.
I want to help, but I'm not strong enough.
Momonosuke.
Listen, my son.
The land of Wano will soon need you.
You have to rebuild the Kozuki clan.
Mother.
Don't worry.
I'm certain that you can do it.
The people of Wano will see your courage.
You'll surely move their hearts.
Hiyori! Father!
I'm counting on you.
I must show my courage, or I will
bring shame to the Kozuki clan!
Momonosuke!
I cannot let everyone's faith go to waste!
I will not give up now!
It's them!
Hey!
Kinamon! Kiku!
You're alive, right?
We're making it through this together!
You hear me?
Don't die!
Strawhat, keep fighting!
You can't stop till Kaido is gone!
You have to free us from Kaido!
Free us, Mr. Stride.
For 20 years, this cruel
battle has continued.
Alas, we cannot finish it alone.
Unless Kaido is vanquished for good,
it will never end!
You fought well today.
I never thought you
could push me this far.
I'm grateful.
And yet, you're still not strong
enough to change this world.
I took it all with my own hands.
I rose to be an emperor of the sea.
That's another win for Kaido!
We're all right, stop above now!
No one in this rotten world can defeat me.
They're all too weak.
You don't know anything, do you?
Our country's trapped in
an endless cycle of war.
We have to keep stealing from other
nations to pay heavenly tributes,
or we'll lose our rights as
a kingdom, as human beings.
We're just slaves of the world government.
You bow to the celestial dragons.
Why not fight back?
You've been drafted.
You're going to become a marine now.
Why would I want to be
a government lapdog?
Let's just say that you're a bit
more than This kingdom can handle.
Shut your damn mouth.
You can't make me do anything.
Let me go. You You bastard!
If you don't, I'll rip you to...
Hand over Kaido as we agreed.
Your country will be given full rights.
You can even join the reverie.
Screw this country!
I'm not your bargaining tool!
Damn it! Not again!
Kaino's on the loose!
Bastard's using us!
He'll get caught again
as soon as he's hungry!
This is a prison ship, not a restaurant!
He's strong!
Who the hell is he?
Look, it says here the guy's only 15.
A bounty like this is
way too high for a kid.
He's a monster!
Hey, brat.
If you want to be a pirate,
this is your chance.
Rox wants to have a talk with you.
Seems you've got a choice to make.
Kaido, join the Rox Privates!
They're invincible now stay
the hell out of their way.
Kaido something big just happened
come on we're headed to god valley.
The rocks pirates are done for but how
what kind of joke is that they had the
strongest pirates in
the world on their crew
i heard a marine named garp took them out.
Nah, I bet they just had a falling out.
They were all power and no teamwork.
Where the hell are you, Kaido?
That little bastard!
I'll kill him.
Kyo, kyo, kyo, kyo.
It's been ten years since then.
Now you've become a one-man army, Kaido.
Kyo, kyo, kyo.
Throughout all of history,
mankind has turned to violence
to solve every problem they face.
As well they should, I say.
We're animals, after all.
The strong have always conquered the weak.
Of course, but what's your point?
The other remnants of the rocks
pirates will grow in power, too,
I'm sure Weapons will decide the
future And I have plenty to spare
the self-appointed rulers of
this world preach peace and they
claim that power is their birthright
will drag them from their thrones
and on to the battlefield
a person's
worth should be determined by
strength that is the only way to
ensure true justice and Freedom!
Sorry, but nothing's going to stop me now!
I heard Yamato talking about Joy Boy.
As for where he learned that
name, I couldn't tell you.
But I know Odin was waiting until he
appeared to open up the borders of Wano.
You're waiting for him
yourself, aren't you?
That's what you said.
In that case, I know
exactly who Joy Boy is.
I cannot afford to be distracted again.
I must trust that Lupi will triumph!
That's the spirit!
Save the land of Wano!
Set its people free!
Make those clowns!
I know you can do it!
Come forth, Flame Clouds!
Heave my call!
The hell is that noise?
No fire can withstand this!
The waters of soul shall deliver you!
Whoa! Water!
It's like they're raining
down from the sky!
Wait, Black Nose!
Don't die! Stay with me!
I'm sorry.
You've had to endure so much pain.
For years and years,
you've remained strong.
I almost lost you there!
Hey, don't get washed away!
Come back!
Where'd this water come from?
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! I did it! Possumey!
Something is happening to the island!
The flame clouds, they're fading!
This is it!
Our time's up! It's falling!
Come forth, flame clouds!
You're amazing!
That should be enough!
Do it!
Stop the island!
You can count on me!
Let's go!
I'll crush every nation under
my heel, just like Wado!
Do you know why you fight?
What kind of world would you create?
Straw Hats!
What do I want?
Luffy!
I want a world where my friends can smile!
Where they can eat until they're full!
Every day!
FIDAL!
Oh, my God.
I said I know who Joy Boy is.
Aren't you curious, King?
Who is it?
He's the man who's going
to defeat me someday.
Then maybe he doesn't exist.